



Seymen Can Aydoğan

O Home: Esenyurt/Aras Sokak/Aşık Veysel Mahallesi, D13 Blok F Girişi / Daire:01, 34510, Istanbul, Türkiye

Email: seymencanofficial@gmail.com **Phone:** (+90) 5374138270

GitHub: https://github.com/seymencanaydogan

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/seymencn/

Date of birth: 04/05/2003 Nationality: Turkish

ABOUT ME

I am Seymen Can. I am 20 years old, a 3rd year computer engineering student at Sakarya University of Applied Sciences. I am improving myself in areas such as machine learning, image processing and am interested in data analysis & science. I am well versed in languages such as Python, C++, C#, SQL. I also have experience in web and mobile programming. I like reading books and watching TV series in my spare time. I am preparing for the industry by actively participating in Artificial Intelligence Student Communities. I also take courses from platforms such as UDEMY and Cambridge. I have a good command of English and I can also speak basic Spanish. I am currently looking for internship offers that will allow me to improve myself further, gain value in the industry and help me understand the field better.

WORK EXPERIENCE

[29/01/2024 - 23/02/2024]

Computer Engineering Intern (.NET Dev)

Istanbul Metropolitan Municipality

City: Istanbul Country: Türkiye

- Got knowledge and skills about .NET Core 8.0 was acquired.
- The project was built in the ASP.NET framework using C# foundations.(https:// github.com/seymencanaydogan/CineMagic-Website-on-ASP.NET)

[02/09/2022 – Current]

Data Scientist Student

SUBU AI (Artificial Intelligence)

City: Sakarya Country: Türkiye

- team-work oriented
- project management
- methodical programming
- advanced python skills
- advanced statistics skills
- knowledge about data analysis, data manipulation
- projects in the field of data science (ex: titanic data set)
- knowledge about machine learning
- projects in the field of machine learning (ex: hotel bookings data set)

VOLUNTEERING

[16/07/2022 - 29/08/2022] ESC Team Volunteering at FITT (Youth Centers UP II) Str. Aries 19, Timisoara 300579, Romania

Youth Centers UP II is a European Solidarity Corps project which aim is to involve international and national volunteers together with the community of Timisoara and Lugoj in solidarity activities. The main purpose of the project is to raise awareness of the power of youth, to develop and strengthen the community through organizing,

promoting and facilitating cultural, educational and leisure activities and events for the public of Timişoara and Lugoj.

Link: https://www.youthpass.eu/en/verify/1213-PTGL-BFWK-3SNA

[29/09/2021 – Current] **Young TEMA** Sakarya University, Sakarya, Turkey

TEMA Foundation is a public movement that was established to combat erosion and protect our natural assets, and today has more than 1 million volunteers. I was a volunteer at TEMA. Youth at the University; It aims to contribute to individuals who are sensitive to the problems of the environment they live in and have an ecological perspective. What Does Young TEMA Do? Sapling planting events and acorn collection events ,awareness activities (walking, flashmob etc.), advocacy work ,nature education studies, booth - promotional activities, supporting the work of TEMA Foundation Representatives, volunteer recruitment activities etc.

[01/01/2023 - Current] **Alpha Community** Istanbul, Turkey

Alpha Community is an international community inspired by the work of the Argentine philosopher and thinker Mario Rodriguez Cobos known as "Silo" (work available on www.silo.net) and is composed of volunteers who are dedicated to the simultaneous social and personal transformation. The founding ideas of Alpha Community are based on the concept of "Ethics of freedom" (overcoming pain and suffering in all human beings) which serves as the central point of view of the analysis about society, psychological dynamics and the approach to the meaning of existence. Alpha Community meets weekly virtually and face-to-face, promoting the development of groups located in various parts of the world, connected to each other in an international multicultural community. Alpha Community is not affiliated with any institution or organization, all the activities promoted are voluntarily self-financed by the participants.

ERASMUS+ YOUTH EX-CHANGES

[14/09/2023 - 19/09/2023] Erasmus+ Project "OUT ON THE FIELDS" in Georgia

The project served as a platform to share experiences and best practices in the field of sports as a tool for social inclusion and aimed to promote the elimination of discrimination. Under the project, the participants had the opportunity to explore and develop their skills and put them into practice with the creation of sessions and projects under the Erasmus+ mobility. The key issues covered are sports, inclusivity, human rights, nondiscrimination, and healthy lifestyles.

Link: https://www.youthpass.eu/en/youthpass/your-certificate/ a62bca6ea22513c4a600d07c0922a9c7-2008262/preview/

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[11/09/2021 – Current]

Computer Engineering at University

Sakarya University of Applied Sciences https://www.subu.edu.tr/en/home

Address: Kemalpaşa, Esentepe Campus, Üniversite Street, Serdivan, 54050, Sakarya

[19/08/2017 - 01/07/2021]

Database Programming at High School

Bahcesehir Borsa Istanbul Technical High School https:// bahcesehirimkb.meb.k12.tr/

City: Istanbul Country: Türkiye

Field(s) of study: Database Final grade: 96,67620 / 100

English C1

Busuu https://api.busuu.com/anon/certificates/d65b8085105a9c6632e9f93410b128e8?lang=en

Country: United Kingdom

AKBANK Machine Learning

Global Al Hub https://globalaihub.com/verify/?

ref=product&certificate=eyJ1c2VyLWlkIjo4MjAwNSwiY291cnNlLWlkIjoxMTk0ODMsImNlcnQtaWQi

AKBANK Data Analysis

Global Al Hub https://globalaihub.com/verify/?

ref=product&certificate=eyJ1c2VyLWlkIjo4MjAwNSwiY291cnNlLWlkIjoxMTgyNDQsImNlcnQtaWQiQ

Artificial Intelligence 101

AKBANK https://akbank-genclik-akademisi.verified.cv/tr/verify/49718999794292

Design 101

AKBANK https://microfon.co/ogrenci/sertifika?

cert=tasarim-101&ke hash=6e1f9b4fc9d89f157c3ba7c7a3f80f629bfe4dfade2d928145040f16c347

Python for Machine Learning

Global AI Hub https://globalaihub.com/verify/?

certificate=eyJ1c2VyLWlkIjo4MjAwNSwiY291cnNlLWlkIjoxMTI4NjQsImNlcnQtaWQiOilxMTMyNjMif0

AYGAZ Deep Learning

Global AI Hub https://globalaihub.com/verify/?

ref=product&certificate=eyJ1c2VyLWlkIjo4MjAwNSwiY291cnNlLWlkIjoxMTk2NTYsImNlcnQtaWQiO

Python from scratch: with ethical hacker examples

Udemy https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/UC-4e090d69-7245-4eee-b070-51418c89f23d.pdf

Social Media Marketing Certificate

Career Development Collage UK https://careerdevelopmentcollege.uk/certificates/4ed9fb674818041b17e5809229d8e334/

City: London

Country: United Kingdom

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Turkish

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1

Spanish

LISTENING A1 READING A1 WRITING A1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION A1 SPOKEN INTERACTION A1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office and Adobe Programs

Microsoft Access | Adobe Premiere, Adobe Premiere pro | Adobe In Design and Photoshop | Teams (Microsoft Teams) | AdobeConnect | Excellent Microsoft Office skills (Outlook, OneDrive, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, etc.) | Adobe Creative Cloud: Acrobad DC, Lightroom, Photoshop

Programming

C# Software Language | C Software Language | Python Software Language | C++ Software Language | Data Analysis, Data Science, Data Visualization | Database: SQL Software Language | Kotlin Software Language | Django - nivel incepator

COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Skills

- Critical Thinking
- Cognitive Flexibility
- · Creativity And Problem Solving
- Good Time Management
- Methodical Programming
- · Detail in Organizational And Planning
- Project Management
- Good Listener And Communicator
- Team-work Oriented
- Respect And Good Atmosphere In Teamwork

Character Traits

- Courageous
- Kind
- Honest And Friendly
- Result-oriented
- Driven
- Motivated
- Dynamic And Energetic Character
- Adventurous
- Orderly
- Positive Attitude

RECOMMENDATIONS

Internship Supervisor

Name: Şule Bayrak

Phone number: (+90) 5314584090 Email: sule.bayrak@ibb.gov.tr

"Aydoğan is a communicative, determined and successful intern"